<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ramblings on SANTI&#39;S MEMEX</title>
    <link>santiachinelli.github.io/categories/ramblings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ramblings on SANTI&#39;S MEMEX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="santiachinelli.github.io/categories/ramblings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Thoughts</title>
      <link>santiachinelli.github.io/post/a_few_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>santiachinelli.github.io/post/a_few_things/</guid>
      <description>Youthful Optimism We use the phrase &amp;lsquo;youthful optimism&amp;rsquo; almost like a linguistic stopgap. It&amp;rsquo;s weight somewhere between &amp;lsquo;a fleeting thing to be desired&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;a backhanded compliment reserved for when my juniors get out of line&amp;rsquo;.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking a lot about the phrase recently, since I started wondering where all the optimistic short science fiction I used to read, 5 or 6 years ago, went. There was Motherboard (nee Vice News) Terraform, which had spit out an enormous amount of great short scifi, along with thematically relavant art, every other week or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nontechnical Meetings</title>
      <link>santiachinelli.github.io/post/better-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>santiachinelli.github.io/post/better-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a meeting structure I have found to be very useful for weekly update meetings. It&amp;rsquo;s a little long for a daily meeting, unless you have a small team.
   Time Activity     10 minutes On a sheet of paper, thoughtfully right out your completed action items from the previous week, and your action items foe the coming week. Identify any potential problems at the end (three sections, 3 minutes per section)   0 minutes Pass the paper to the person to your left   1 minute Review and mentally prepare to pitch and represent your coworker’s week   3 minutes Explain their week to the group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>